organicauthority.com 2019-06-09

# Privacy Policy - Organic Authority

We use Ezoic to provide personalization and analytic services on this website, as such Ezoic's privacy policy is in effect and can be reviewed [here](http://g.ezoic.net/privacy/organicauthority.com).  

This is the web site of **OrganicAuthority.com**.

Our postal address is:

 **Organic Authority, Inc.**  
 **9854 National Blvd. #413  
Los Angeles, CA 90034**

We can be reached via e-mail at [liveorganic@organicauthority.com](http://www.organicauthority.com/mailto:liveorganic@organicauthority.com)  
or you can reach us by telephone at 310-694-8306

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes the consumer’s domain name and e-mail address (where possible).

We collect the domain name and e-mail address (where possible) of visitors to our Web page, the e-mail addresses of those who post messages to our bulletin board, the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, user-specific information on what pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations, name and address, telephone number, fax number, payment information (e.g., credit card number and billing address).

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web page, notify consumers about updates to our Web site, and to contact consumers for marketing purposes.

As we continue to develop our business, we might sell certain of our assets in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, sale of assets, or other corporate change respecting the Web site. In such transactions, user information, including personally identifiable information, generally is on of the transferred business assets, and by submitting your personal information on the Website you agree that your data may be transferred to such parties in these circumstances.

With respect to cookies: We use cookies to record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, alert visitors to new areas that we think might be of interest to them when they return to our site, record past activity at a site in order to provide better service when visitors return to our site.

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on your (the user) prior visits to our website and other websites. These ads do not necessarily reflect the views of Organic Authority staff or sponsors. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to you based on your history of visits to our site and/or other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). You can also opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative [opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by writing to us at the above address.

We never share or sell your personal information, unless we need to do so in order to provide a product or service that you have requested. We guarantee adherence to industry best practices that ensure complete security, and we fully comply with all federal regulations. If we change our privacy policy, we will tell you.

If you supply us with your postal address on-line you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by writing to us at the above address.

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line may receive telephone contact from us with information regarding new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such telephone calls, please let us know by writing to us at the above address.

Please provide us with your name and phone number. We will be sure your name is removed from the list we share with other organizations.

We may retain other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include data analysis firms, customer support specialists, web hosting companies, and fulfillment companies (e.g. companies that coordinate mailings). Such third parties may be provided with access to personally identifiable information needed to perform their functions, but may not use such information for any other purpose. Such third parties may also use the information collected in aggregate form for their internal business purposes, such as generating statistics for marketing materials.

With respect to Ad Servers: To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and click stream information.

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Website to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.

This website contains links to and from other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. This Privacy Statement applies only to the information we collect on this Website. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of other websites you link to from our Website or otherwise visit.

We do not provide site visitors with access to information that we have collected and that we maintain about them.

Access to this website and its content is provided without charge to users “AS IS” and without warranty of any kind. We shall bear no responsibility or liability for any damages of any kind arising out or in connection with, the use copying or display of content from this website.

The opinions and views expressed by the authors at Organic Authority in blogs and on social media and more, are theirs alone and do not necessarily reflect the views, opinions or position of Organic Authority, Inc and do not necessarily represent the views of Organic Authority sponsors and/or partners. Organic Authority content is for informational and entertainment purposes, and any views expressed should not be accepted as a substitute for qualified expertise. Any highlighted alternative studies are intended to spark conversation and are for information purposes only. We are not here to diagnose or treat any health or medical conditions, nor should this be relied upon as a substitute for professional medical advice, diagnosis or treatment, even if it features the advice of medical practitioners and physicians. When making any lifestyle or health changes, consult your primary care physician.

Though we make every effort to provide accurate information, it is up to you, the reader, to use Organic Authority’s content responsibly; in return, we promise to publish responsibly. If we make a mistake, we will take whatever reasonable course of action we can to acknowledge and correct it. (Fortunately, this doesn’t happen too often.) We appreciate our readers keeping us sharp, and take our role in informing, sharing and expressing seriously. We value your trust.
